Denis Korenyako

Product Designer with 15+ years of background in UI/UX. Experience in producing efficient user-centered design solutions from defining the problem to delivering a final product. Strong skills in ideation and art direction. Able to function as a project leader as well as an individual contributor. Passionate about customer experience and all aspects of design.

Phone: +7 (905) 000-4567

Email: den89@mail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/korenyaaa8k

Country of residence: Russia, ready to relocate, Visa

assistance needed

PORTFOLIO

www.portfolio.url

EXPERIENCE

Digital Manager — De Fonseca, Moscow

MAY 2018 - PRESENT

Italian home slippers brand №1

- Managed all digital activities of De Fonseca in Russia.
- Designed the global website with localization in multiple languages.
- Created a UX that resulted in 53% increase of conversion rate.
- Built and delivered a digital strategy which led to a 388% increase of online sales
- Increased brand awareness and achieved 5x increase in branded search traffic

Art Director — Leto, Moscow

AUGUST 2016 - APRIL 2018

Russian leading digital agency, part of Ark Scholz & Friends Group

- Oversaw the art direction and design for a variety of clients including Anheuser-Busch, Bosch, Ferrero, Hyundai, Imperial Tobacco, Mercedes- Benz, PepsiCo, Philip Morris, KFC, Kotányi, Mazda, SCA (Essity), Pizza Hut, Saint-Gobain, Unilever, Valio, X5 Group.
- Led the UX/UI of the client's internal app from scratch to delivery that
 - effectively saved POS maintenance costs up to 70%
- Led the website design for a leading food retailer from analytics and user research to production-ready UI.
- Built new internal processes for rapid design and prototyping with InVision
 and Marvel

Designer — **KupiVIP**, Moscow

NOVEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2016

Largest Russian flash sales website, backed by Accel, Intel and Mangrove

- Designed the website with 1,5 million MAU being the only UX/UI designer in the company.
- Accomplished project in a strict deadline timeframe

Designer — SpaceBox, Moscow

MAY 2014 - OCTOBER 2015

Design consultancy specialized in e-commerce and large-scale intranet portals

SKILLS

UX: prototypes, mockups, analysis, user flows, personas

Tools: Figma, Photoshop, InVision, Marvel, Excel, PowerPoint, Jira

Methodologies: Agile, Design Thinking, Customer Development, Customer Journey Map, Jobs-to-be done

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Google Digital Garage,

The Fundamentals of digital marketing

JUNE 2021

Google Analytics, Google Analytics Individual Qualification

JUNE 2021

Accenture, Digital Skills: User Experience MAY 2020

- Designed a CRM for the biggest Russian online library.
- Conceptualized the intranet UI for one of the largest real estate companies
- Successfully designed websites for six company clients.

EDUCATION

Russian Academy of Public Administration, Moscow — Diploma

NOVEMBER 2005 - AUGUST 2006

Passed final exam with Distinction Television director, Diploma

Moscow State University of Printing Arts, Moscow

— Uncompleted

SEPTEMBER 1996 - JANUARY 2001

Completed 5173 hours towards a BFA.

EXPERIENCE (continued)

Product Manager — Apartama, Moscow

SEPTEMBER 2011 - FEBRUARY 2014

Startup, social commerce platform and furnishing marketplace

- Initiated and completed redesign that led to a 5% (1:20) conversion.
- Boosted number of user registrations, increased customer purchases by 34%
- Progressed with the company's growth, beginning as a designer and promoted to product manager.
- Spearheaded a cross-functional team of 5.

Lead Web Designer — KM, Moscow

SEPTEMBER 2010 - AUGUST 2011

The oldest Russian news portal and encyclopedia

- Led redesign of the main website with 3+ million MAU
- Created 120+ unique pages ahead of schedule.

Designer — **RBC Soft**, Moscow

AUGUST 2009 - SEPTEMBER 2010

Major Russian software company, part of RBC (RosBusinessConsulting) media group

- Designed Russian government websites for Ministry of Telecom and Mass Communications, Ministry of Economic Development and Federal Service for Supervision in Education and Science.
- Developed numerous PowerPoint decks which helped to secure over \$5 million in funding and investments.

Designer, **DJEM Solutions**, Moscow

OCTOBER 2007 - MARCH 2009

Art Director, BCD Group, Moscow

MAY 2003 - SEPTEMBER 2007

Art Director, New Publishing Projects, Moscow

JULY 2002 - MAY 2003

Web Designer, EuroAddress, Moscow

OCTOBER 2001 - JUNE 2002

Designer, Gazeta.ru, Moscow

SEPTEMBER 1999 - OCTOBER 2001

Web Designer, Triumvirate, Moscow

OCTOBER 1998 — MAY 1999

Game Artist, ElectroTECH Multimedia, Moscow

SEPTEMBER 1997 — MARCH 1998